<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Awesome Learning]]></title><description><![CDATA[Learning frontend, together]]></description><link>https://wayfair.github.io/awesome-learning/</link><generator>RSS for Node</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2019 19:03:57 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title><![CDATA[Data Types]]></title><description><![CDATA[The focus of this course is to make you familiar with the nuance of the JavaScript Data Types. A little hazy on passing objects by reference? Not sure why your number is coercing to a string? Not sure what coercion is? Then this is the topic for you. Feel at home with the data types and how to make them do what you want by the end of this course]]></description><link>https://wayfair.github.io/awesome-learning//courses/Data-Types/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://wayfair.github.io/awesome-learning//courses/Data-Types/</guid><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Functions and Scope]]></title><description><![CDATA[If you want to learn about JavaScript functions, then this is the course for you. Did you know that everything is a function? No? How about binding functions to Objects? Closures? Learn the digestible rules of arrow functions and when to use them best. What the heck is a this anyway? Become familiar with scope and context in JavaScript and use them to your advantage. By the end of this course, you will become familiar with all of these topics and more.]]></description><link>https://wayfair.github.io/awesome-learning//courses/Functions-and-Scope/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://wayfair.github.io/awesome-learning//courses/Functions-and-Scope/</guid><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Array Methods]]></title><description><![CDATA[Welcome to the Awesome Learning Array Methods course. Over the next 5 lessons, you will deep dive into the 4 most commonly used array methods.]]></description><link>https://wayfair.github.io/awesome-learning//courses/Array-Methods/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://wayfair.github.io/awesome-learning//courses/Array-Methods/</guid><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Promises]]></title><description><![CDATA[Asynchronous programming patterns are the cornerstone of Frontend. All of the interactive interfaces we build on the web would not be possible without the asynchronous features of JavaScript. This course will teach you the crucial nuance when utilizing these patterns and will heavily focus on Promises]]></description><link>https://wayfair.github.io/awesome-learning//courses/Promises/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://wayfair.github.io/awesome-learning//courses/Promises/</guid><content:encoded>&lt;div class=&quot;gatsby-highlight&quot; data-language=&quot;text&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;         &lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Testing]]></title><description><![CDATA[Welcome to the Automated Testing course. Over the upcoming weeks you will dive into  frontend testing using Jest and eventually Enzyme. By the end of this track you will know how  to test user interfaces, as well as user interactions.]]></description><link>https://wayfair.github.io/awesome-learning//courses/Testing/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://wayfair.github.io/awesome-learning//courses/Testing/</guid><content:encoded></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>